I really didn't expect
his methods to be so ruthless.
No wonder Young Master Long hurried away with his men last night.
If I had followed them,
this wouldn't have happened.
How about we try again?
Actually, there is still a turning point.
What turning point?
My father has a notebook
that records
the secrets of those in power
to control them.
As long as we can get our hands on that notebook,
no one will be able to protect him anymore.
Indeed.
If we don't get that notebook,
we won't be able to catch him no matter how many times we try.
Where is the notebook?
At home.
We need to split up.
Lawyer Gu and I will find a way to stall the others
and make sure no one is at my father's house.
When the time comes,
you sneak into the house and get the notes.
We have limited time.
I'll leave everything to you.
Sir.
Are you the one who needs a lock opened?
Please come in.
You want to open this lock?
Can you open it?
I can open it,
but it will take some time.
I'll pay extra.
I'll open it right away.
Look at Yangyang.
Once he's on stage,
his charisma really shows.
Yes, it's really different.
I had the company's operations department
create content specifically for Yangyang,
along with a follow-up incubation plan.
With me as his brother,
in less than ten posts,
I'll definitely make Yangyang go viral.
Viral or not, traffic or no traffic,
it doesn't matter.
As long as Yangyang likes it, that's fine.
Yangyang is my own brother.
I will definitely give him the best.
Thank you for your trouble.
Dad.
Why are you here?
Wait for me outside.
Let's go.
What exactly is going on?
I'm talking about last night.
Right after you brought the person into the room,
the police received a call.
I found out through a friend
that the call was made from the exhibition room.
Everyone at the exhibition has worked with me before.
They would never betray me.
Only you guys
have nothing to do with me.
Father.
I know
I can't lie to you,
because you'll find out sooner or later.
You've always been omnipotent.
I was the one who called the police.
What a sin.
What exactly do you want?
Father.
Because I'm scared.
I'm afraid you'll keep making mistakes
and end up on the path of crime.
It's not too late to turn back now.
Father.
Haven't you always taught me since I was little
that in everything we do,
we must not go against our conscience?
Dad.
I really can't bear
to see you keep making mistakes.
Go turn yourself in.
Okay?
Remember what you said.
Hurry.
Notify Brother Chen immediately.
Okay.
Ling Hengsheng has gone back.
Hurry up.
Are you done yet?
Almost.
Don't worry, boss.
Dad, I want to take a video of you next time.
Okay, get in the car first.
Get in.
Send someone to monitor Lingze.
And check on that lawyer again.
Understood.
I want to livestream.
I'm going to livestream.
Your family is back.
None of your business. Keep driving.
Dad, I want a company like yours too.
I want one like yours too.
Those companies of mine are all prepared for you.
Go back to your room and rest first.
Take him back.
Let's go.
It's open.
Got it.
Your father sent you.
Go back and tell him.
I know what to say and what not to say.
Tell him to keep his promise.
You misunderstood, Uncle Zhao.
I came
for you.
Uncle Zhao.
We know that over the years,
you were forced to help Ling Hengsheng
do many illegal deals.
These are
the means he uses to threaten you,
right?
Who is she?
She is a lawyer,
the daughter of that reporter from back then.
Do you want it?
Let me look at you.
Do you want it or not?
Can you even fight?
We already have enough evidence.
As long as you're willing to cooperate and testify,
I believe...
Enough.
Do you know what you're doing?
You're crazy.
Going against your father?
He is Ling Hengsheng.
Just now,
I didn't hear anything.
Wait.
Please give me a little more time,
and give yourself a chance,
if you don't want to be controlled by him forever.
What else do you want?
Hey, are you okay?
They are all safe and sound.
Honey.
Dad.
Honey,
son,
I'm
sorry.
It's all my fault.
Dad, where are you?
When are you coming to pick us up?
Don't worry about us.
This young man saved us.
Okay.
Don't cry.
Chenyao.
It's okay now.
You must ensure the safety of Uncle Zhao's family.
Rest assured.
Uncle Zhao,
for the sake of your family and children,
stop fostering crime
and condoning it.
Cooperate with us.
Okay.
I can't believe
that person's daughter
has been hiding right under our noses for so long.
-Who did this?
Uncle Zhao's family has been rescued.
I don't know who did it.
Get ready to leave immediately.
Wait until things cool down,
then get rid of her.
And
Ling Ze.
Okay.
Hurry.
Ah Long.
What are you doing?
Where is Ling Hengsheng?